Aseel Al Sabahi

Orlando, FL • (407) 451-7747 • aseelalsabahi@knights.ucf.edu • www.linkedin.com/in/aseelalsabahi

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

International student with more than four years of extensive volunteering, marketing, communication, and customer service experience. Has excellent analytical, organizational, and planning skills, as well as being self-drive, an effective team member, and pays attention to details. Wants to expand marketing abilities into finance, accounting, and business industries while sharing and gaining experience.

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida

December 2021

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, Finance (GPA: 3.806)

Honors:

Knights in Shining Armor- Global UCF

President Honor Roll

Dean's List- College of Business

WORK EXPERIENCE

Orlando Premier Consulting, Orlando, FL

August 2021-Present 2021

Business Management Trainee

- Presenting and promoting products while keeping track of sales through regular sales reports.
- Attending team and client meetings to discuss sales and marketing strategies.
- Travelling to various marketing events.

EmployerNomics, REMOTE

May 2021-July 2021

PEO Sales Representative

- Networked, connected, and met with different clients.
- Presented and promoted services.

University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL

September 2020-December 2020

Peer Advocate in Wellness and Health Promotion Services

- Reinforced healthy behaviors and assisted in keeping our campus healthy.
- Gave out incentive items for students displaying healthy behaviors.

National Bank of Oman, Muscat, Oman

June 2019-July 2019

Internship, Banking Customer Service Representative

- Helped clients to solve issues in an effective and friendly manner.
- Aided Cardholders with account questions, billing transactions, financial plans and promotions.
- Assisted customers with credit line increases/decrease inquiries, disputes, and account education.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE AND ACTIVITIES

Member - Omani Orlando Student Association

October 2019 – Present 2021

Member - Wasm volunteer team

May 2017 – Present 2021

Member - Volunteer UCF

April 2019 – Present 2021

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Languages: English, Arabic, and Turkish

Computer Skills: Microsoft Office (Word- PowerPoint- Excel- OneNote)

Skills: Interpersonal, verbal, and written communication, sales and marketing, customer service, problem

solving, patience, time management.

Certifications: Excel: Creating a Basic Dashboard (Project Management institute) & Being an Effective Team

Member